module.exports = [
 {
   question: 'How much money has the "Marvel Cinematic Universe" grossed since 2008?',
   a: '$4.21 Billion',
   b: '$4.66 Billion',
   c: '$5.96 Billion',
   d: '$6.82 Billion',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: 'What was the original name of Marvel Comics?',
   a: 'Timely Publications',
   b: 'Marvelous Comics',
   c: 'Fantastic Adventures',
   d: 'National Allied Publications',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'What is the most expensive film ever made?',
   a: 'Avengers: Infinity War',
   b: 'Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides',
   c: 'Justice League',
   d: 'Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'What is Stan Lee\'s birth name?',
   a: 'Stanley Lee',
   b: 'Stanley Leibowitz',
   c: 'Stanley Laurence',
   d: 'Stanley Lieber',
   answer: 'd'
 },
 {
   question: 'What is the worst rated comic book movie, according to Rotten Tomatoes?',
   a: 'The Crow: Wicked Prayer',
   b: 'I Frankenstein',
   c: 'Catwoman',
   d: 'Batman vs. Superman: Dawn of Justice',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'How many times has Robert Downey Jr. played Iron Man?',
   a: '10',
   b: '9',
   c: '8',
   d: '7',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which character is not owned by Marvel Studios?',
   a: 'Captain Marvel',
   b: 'Green Lantern',
   c: 'Elektra',
   d: 'Hank Pym',
   answer: 'b'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which actor is not currently part of the Marvel Cinematic Universe?',
   a: 'William Hurt',
   b: 'Martin Freeman',
   c: 'Felicity Jones',
   d: 'Evangeline Lilly',
   answer: 'c'
 },
 {
   question: 'Which character does Idris Elba play in the Marvel movies?',
   a: 'Heimdall',
   b: 'Tanngrisnir',
   c: 'Loki',
   d: 'Donar',
   answer: 'a'
 },
 {
   question: 'How old is Chris Pratt?',
   a: '39',
   b: '40',
   c: '35',
   d: '38',
   answer: 'd'
 },
];